directresponse.net 2011-10-07

# Privacy Policy

                                   Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Last Updated: February 9, 2011
DirectResponse.net strives to offer its visitors the many advantages of Internet
technology and to provide an interactive and personalized experience. We may use
Personally Identifiable Information (your name, e-mail address, street address,
telephone number) subject to the terms of this privacy policy. We will never sell, barter,
or rent your email address to any unauthorized third party. Period.
How we gather information from users
How we collect and store information depends on the page you are visiting, the activities
in which you elect to participate and the services provided. For example, you may be
asked to provide information when you register for access to certain portions of our site
or request certain features, such as newsletters or when you make a purchase. You may
provide information when you participate in sweepstakes and contests, message boards
and chat rooms, and other interactive areas of our site. Like most Web sites,
DirectResponse.net also collects information automatically and through the use of
electronic tools that may be transparent to our visitors. For example, we may log the
name of your Internet Service Provider or use cookie technology to recognize you and
hold information from your visit. Among other things, the cookie may store your user
name and password, sparing you from having to re-enter that information each time you
visit, or may control the number of times you encounter a particular advertisement
while visiting our site. As we adopt additional technology, we may also gather
information through other means. In certain cases, you can choose not to provide us
with information, for example by setting your browser to refuse to accept cookies, but if
you do you may be unable to access certain portions of the site or may be asked to re-

enter your user name and password, and we may not be able to customize the site’s
features according to your preferences.
What we do with the information we collect
Like other Web publishers, we collect information to enhance your visit and deliver
more individualized content and advertising. We respect your privacy and do not share
your information with anyone.
Aggregated Information (Information that does not personally indentify you) may be
used in many ways. For example, we may combine information about your usage
patterns with similar information obtained from other users to help enhance our site
and services (e.g., to learn which pages are visited most or what features are most
attractive). Aggregated information may occasionally be shared with other advertisers
and business partners. Again, this information does not include any Personally
Identifiable Information about you or allow anyone to identify you individually.
We may use Personally Identifiable Information collected on DirectResponse.net to
communicate with you about our registration and customization preferences; our Terms
of Service and privacy policy; services and products offered by DirectResponse.net and
other topics we think you might find of interest.
Personally Identifiable Information collected by DirectResponse.net may also be used
for other purposes, including but not limited to site administration, troubleshooting,
processing of ecommerce transactions, administration of sweepstakes and contests, and
other communications with you. Certain third parties who provide technical support for
the operation of our site (our Web hosting service for example) may access such
information. We will use your information only as permitted by law. In addition, from
time to time as we continue to develop our business, we may sell, buy, merge or partner
with other companies or businesses. In such transactions, user information may be
among the transferred assets. We may also disclose your information in response to do
so by law, in connection with the collection of amounts you may owe to us, and/or to law
enforcement authorities whenever we deem it appropriate or necessary. Please note we
may not provide you with notice prior to disclosure in such cases.
Affiliated sites, linked sites and advertisements
DirectResponse.net expects its partners, advertisers and affiliates to respect the privacy
of our users. Be aware, however, that third parties, including our partners, advertisers,
affiliates and other content providers accessible through our site, may have their own
privacy and data collection policies and practices. For example, during your visit to our
site you may link to, or view as part of a frame on a DirectResponse.net page, certain
content that is actually created or hosted by a third party. Also, through

DirectResponse.net you may be introduced to, or be able to access, information,
websites, features, contests or sweepstakes offered by other parties. DirectResponse.net
is not responsible for the actions or policies of such third parties. You should check the
applicable privacy policies of those third parties when providing information on a
feature or page operated by a third party.
While on our site, our advertisers, promotional partners or other third parties may use
cookies or other technology to attempt to identify some of your preferences or retrieve
information about you. For example, some of our advertising is served by third parties
and may include cookies that enable the advertiser to determine whether you have seen
a particular advertisement before. Other features available on our site may offer services
operated by third parties and may use cookies or other technology to gather
information. DirectResponse.net does not control the use of this technology by third
parties or the resulting information, and is not responsible for any actions or policies of
such third parties.
You should also be aware that if you voluntarily disclose Personally Identifiable
Information on message boards or in chat areas, that information can be viewed
publicly and can be collected and used by third parties without our knowledge and may
result in unsolicited messages from other individuals or third parties. Such activities are
beyond the control of DirectResponse.net and this policy.
Children
DirectResponse.net does not knowingly collect or solicit Personally Identifiable
Information from or about children under 13 except as permitted by law. If we discover
we have received any information from a child under 13 in violation of this policy, we
will delete that information immediately. If you believe DirectResponse.net has any
information from or about anyone under 13, please contact us at the address listed
below.
Contacting Us
We can be reached by contacting:
DirectResponse.net
Email: info@DirectResponse.net
Changes to this policy
DirectResponse.net reserves the right to change this policy at any time. Please check this
page periodically for changes. Your continued use of our site following the posting of
changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes. Information collected prior

to the time any change is posted will be used according to the rules and laws that applied
at the time the information was collected.
Governing Law
This policy and the use of this Site are governed by Delaware Law. If a dispute arises
under this Policy we agree to first try to resolve it with the help of a mutually agreed-
upon mediator in the following location: Delaware. Any costs and fees other than
attorney fees associated with the mediation will be shared equally between us.
If it proves impossible to arrive at a mutually satisfactory solution through mediation,
we agree to submit the dispute binding arbitration at the following location: Delaware,
under the rules of the American Arbitration Association. Judgment upon the award
rendered by the arbitration may be entered in any court with jurisdiction to do so.
DirectResponse.net is controlled, operated and administered entirely within Delaware.
This statement and the policies outlined herein are not intended to and do not create
any contractual or other legal rights in or on behalf of any party.
